honda.co.uk 2015-06-19

# Privacy Policy | Honda (UK)

Personal Information and Transfers of such information gathered by Honda.co.uk is controlled by Honda (UK), a division of Honda Motor Europe Limited, located at:

Cain Road  
Bracknell  
Berkshire  
RG12 1HL

**Information Collection and Use**  
Honda (UK) is the sole owner of the information collected on this Web site. Data that you provide will only be shared by Honda, its associated companies, authorised dealers or third parties working on behalf of Honda. We or they may wish to contact you regarding our products, services, offers, technical developments or your opinions which may be used for marketing, research or analysis purposes. 

Honda.co.uk collects the following types of information:

**Contact Details**  
We collect your contact details when you: 

  * subscribe to receive one of our e-communications
  * order a brochure;
  * book a test drive
  * register a product or change your vehicle ownership details 
  * enquire about a specific product
  * request a call back
  * respond to a campaign
  * submit a question to us or provide us with feedback

You are provided with an opportunity to opt out from receiving communications from us or our partners at the time that your details are submitted.  
Back to top

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on your computer's hard drive that contains some minimal information about you. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to personally identifiable information while you are visiting our web site and it actually facilitates your ability to use our site. If you want to disable the cookie, log out or select "delete cookies" under Internet Options on your tool bar.  
Back to top

**Fake emails using Honda's name**  
Honda is aware of fake emails, popularly called "phishing" emails regarding job advertisements, job offers and competition award notifications. These emails use Honda’s name to pretend they are genuine and exist solely for the purpose of obtaining private information about consumers (e.g. credit card numbers or passwords). These emails have no connection with Honda and Honda does not use these methods for job advertising or competition / award winner activity. 

Unfortunately these fake emails are a growing fraud on the Internet. This practice is carried out either by the sending of a bogus email directly to a victim, or by directing them to a website where personal information is requested.

You can usually identify a fake job offer from Honda, as there will be many inconsistencies throughout the document. Recent examples have been sent from ‘Honda Motor Company UK’ (which is not a valid legal entity). The email has then directed people to make a payment to a false UK based solicitor firm, using the name ‘Clifford Chambers Solicitors’. Neither is connected to Honda in any way. 

Fake job offers tend to target overseas individuals, as they ask for money to be sent to them for UK visa purposes. Honda never requests payments details in association with any job applications or any communication related to them. If in any doubt about the validity of a recruitment offer, please contact [huk.recruitment@honda-eu.com](mailto:huk.recruitment@honda-eu.com)

Recent email award notifications have purported to be from the Honda Security Department, Honda's Lottery Department and Honda Grand Promotions UK. Honda never requests payments details in association with competition winners or any communication related to them.

Honda advises that if you receive an email using Honda’s name and asking for personal information or financial information and have concerns about its authenticity, then please treat such emails with extreme caution.   
Back to top

### Website Activity

 **** **Correcting/Updating/Accessing Personal Information**  
If your personal information changes (such as post code, email address, etc.), or if we have inaccurate information, we will endeavour to correct, update or remove your personal information from our database. To notify us of a change or inaccuracy, you can advise us using our [Update your Details form](http://www.honda.co.uk/cars/owners/you-and-your-car/update-your-details/) or by calling us on **0845 200 8000**.  
Back to top

### Subject Access Requests

If you would like to access the personal information that Honda holds about you, please write to us at Cain Road, Bracknell, Berkshire, RG12 1HL for the attention of the Company Solicitor. Please include a payment of £10 payable to Honda (UK) to cover administration and processing costs.  
Back to top

**Choice/Opt-in and Opt-out**  
You will be given the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out to having your contact details used for purposes not directly related to our web site. For example, when you order a brochure, you can tell us when you provide your details, if you do not want to receive any other information from Honda or our partners, or you can let us know how best to get in touch with you with information that may be of interest.  
If you no longer wish to receive email or other promotional materials from us, you may opt-out of receiving these communications at any time by one of the following methods:  

  * by replying to the email with ‘unscubscribe’ in the subject line
  * by using the opt out boxes on the response form and submitting it
  * by writing to the Database Manager, Honda (UK), Cain Road, Bracknell, Berkshire, RG12 1HL, United Kingdom
  * by calling us on 0845 200 800

Back to top

**Links to Third Party Sites**  
Honda is not responsible for the content of any web sites that are linked to its site. When entering a third party site, it is your responsibility to ensure that you read the Privacy Policy and Legal Terms & Conditions that apply to that site.  
Back to top

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use your personal data in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by email. You will have a choice as to whether or not we use the information in this different manner.  
Back to top

**Security**  
We take every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit personal information via the web site, the information is password protected both online and off-line.  
Back to top
